var readlineSync = require('readline-sync');
var userName = readlineSync.question("May I know your name ???");
console.log("Hello "+userName +",Welcome to do you know Nagarjuna???... Quiz!");
var score = 0 ;

var highscores = [
  {
    name : "Nagarjuna",
    score : "5"
  },
  {name : "buddy",
   score: "4",}
]

function play (questions , answer)
{
var userAnswer = readlineSync.question(questions);
 if(userAnswer === answer){
   console.log("You are right!!!");
   score = score + 1 ;
 }
 else
 {
   console.log("You are wrong!!!");
 }
 console.log ("Score :"+ score );
 console.log("---------");
}
var questions =
 [
  {
    question : "what is my age?",
    answer : "21",
  },
   
   {
     question : "what is my home town?",
    answer : "guntur",
    }
   ,
  {
    question : "where do i study?",
    answer : "manipal",
  },
  {
    question : "which year am I studying ?",
    answer : "3",
  },
  {
    question : "which branch?",
    answer : "ece",
  } 
 ]

  for (i=0 ; i<questions.length; i++ )
  {
    currentquestion = questions[i]
    play(currentquestion.question , currentquestion.answer);
  }

  console.log(" Congrats... Your total  score is : ", score);
  
   console.log("___________________");
  console.log("These are the highscores if you score more than this send me a screenshot");

  for(i=0 ; i<highscores.length;i++)
  {
   var currenthighscore = highscores[i];
   console.log(currenthighscore.name,currenthighscore.score)
  }

 var readlineSync = require('readline-sync');
var userName = readlineSync.question("May I know your name ???");
console.log("Hello "+userName +",Welcome to do you know Nagarjuna???... Quiz!");
var score = 0 ;

var highscores = [
  {
    name : "Nagarjuna",
    score : "5"
  },
  {name : "buddy",
   score: "4",}
]

function play (questions , answer)
{
var userAnswer = readlineSync.question(questions);
 if(userAnswer === answer){
   console.log("You are right!!!");
   score = score + 1 ;
 }
 else
 {
   console.log("You are wrong!!!");
 }
 console.log ("Score :"+ score );
 console.log("---------");
}
var questions =
 [
  {
    question : "what is my age?",
    answer : "21",
  },
   
   {
     question : "what is my home town?",
    answer : "guntur",
    }
   ,
  {
    question : "where do i study?",
    answer : "manipal",
  },
  {
    question : "which year am I studying ?",
    answer : "3",
  },
  {
    question : "which branch?",
    answer : "ece",
  } 
 ]

  for (i=0 ; i<questions.length; i++ )
  {
    currentquestion = questions[i]
    play(currentquestion.question , currentquestion.answer);
  }

  console.log(" Congrats... Your total  score is : ", score);
  
   console.log("___________________");
  console.log("These are the highscores if you score more than this send me a screenshot");

  for(i=0 ; i<highscores.length;i++)
  {
   var currenthighscore = highscores[i];
   console.log(currenthighscore.name,currenthighscore.score)
  }

 